



MATTIA BACCO

Webmaster



In my journey I've worked on the frontend as on the backend, fixing bugs, building synchronicities and wizards for improving the quality of life of my colleagues. In the last period I've been actively participating in the renovation process of the new ecommerce, doing benchmarks, organizing providers and, working in the marketing team, I've been able to learn some new skills.

In my free time I love taking pictures and learning new skills, such as 3D modelling and Photo Editing software.

EDUCATION

- Computer Expert Diploma | ITIS Severi 2009-2014
- .NET C# Course 2015
- Google UX Design
 Professional Certificate
 2021 Today (4 of 7 Certificates)

SKILLS

Development Skills

ASP .NET C# SQL PHP HTML - SCSS - JS

Soft Skills

Communication Creativity Analytical Skills Time Management Team Work

EXPERIENCE

INTERNSHIP AS WEB DESIGNER

SnapSystem 2015 - 6 Month

As intern in SnapSystem, i've built their Wordpress site, gaining confidence with the CMS platform.

IT CONSULTANT IN C#

Consoft Informatica 2015 - 2016

Consoft Informatica is a consultant agency, where I did a C# course. For Consoft I've worked in a C# Developer team as Junior.

IT DEVELOPER IN C#

Galileo Network 2016-2018

In Galileo Network I've worked on the visual refacing of their software. Beyond working on the frontend, in this 3 years I've worked on Stored Procedure and Bank related features of the company property software.

WEBMASTER - MARKETING TEAM

Silikomart 2018 - Now

My experience at Silikomart can be organized in three chapters, the first one being the bug fixing and backend implementation of an existing ecommerce (custom built in ASP).

The second one being the developing a Magento 1 based ecommerce, which lasted 2 years. In this period i've done several activities such as sync for custom db, custom template and custom module for the platform. The last one, consists on the project for the new ecommerce, to whom i've done several benchmarking, search for the right tool and feasibility study